In the picture window, double-click to open the British Files folder.
Find the D in the scene details, Constructing a fly and zipper closure.
Drag it to the 2D or 3D window on the PantsFly file.
Since the British Files is not symmetrical, create one by copying and pasting.
Use the Adjustment Files tool.
In the 2D window, right-click on the British Files and select Copy.
Right-click on the British Files and select Paste.
The shadow of the copied Files will move with the mouse,
until it is released.
Click on the 2D window to release it.
Be careful not to overlap the Files.
Use the Automatic Filing tool to merge the left-hander and the right-hander Files.
Note that the Filing type needs to be modified to Tint.
After simulation, the Hander will be more flat.
Use the Automatic Filing tool to merge the left-hander Files and the right-hander Files.
Use the Automatic Filing tool to merge the left-hander Files and the left-hander Files.
Use the Collar Expansion tool to select the base line on the right-hander Files.
Then press the return key on the keyboard to create an inner line.
Use the Automatic Filing tool to merge the left-hander Files to the left-hander Files.
In the 3D window, select the right-hander Files.
Then press the right-hand button on the Files.
Select Add to the menu.
In the 3D window, use the Location tool to place another Files into it.
Check the gap between the Files.
Use the Iceberg tool to press the right-hand button on the right-hand side of the iceberg.
In the menu, select the inner line.
Enter the value and click OK.
Use the Line Filling tool to merge the newly created inner lines.
Activate the simulation and set it to 3D clothing.
In the 2D window, press the right-hand button on the left-hander Files.
In the
Select the inner line and delete it.
Use the High-quality clothing tool to click OK.
Activate the simulation and set it to 3D clothing.
In the Selection set all people and movement to the right-hand side.
Execute the simulation and select the right-hand side.
In the following window, that sea-few-hee-doe can be powiedzed as black.
Everything is habitable.
Let crown text appear.
Press Ctrl M.
Press Enter.
Bring booted sheet touch.